<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../src-generated/schemas/fhir-single.xsd" lang="en">
  <a name="scope">  </a>
	<p>
    This is our FHIR Implementation Guide. It contains the specifications developed by our community. 
   </p>
	<blockquote class="stu-note">
	<strong>This documentation and set of artefacts are still undergoing development.</strong>
	This content is only for demonstrative purposes.
	</blockquote>
	<p> </p>
  <h3>Content</h3> <a name="content"> </a>
	<p/>

<p>This publication contains the full set of specifications...</p>
<p></p>
<p>There is also an overview of the projects and motivation for the specifications.</p>
<p></p>

<a name="navigation"> </a>
<p>The top menu allows quick navigation to the different sections, and a <a href="toc.html">Table of Contents</a> is provided with the entire content of this Implementation Guide. (Be aware that some pages have multiple tabs).</p>
<p></p>
	<a name="ip"> </a>
	<h3>Intellectual Property Considerations</h3>
	<p>
    While this implementation guide and the underlying FHIR are licensed as public domain, this guide includes examples making use of terminologies such 
    as LOINC, SNOMED CT and others which have more restrictive licensing requirements. Implementers should make themselves familiar with licensing and 
    any other constraints of terminologies, questionnaires, and other components used as part of their implementation process. In some cases, 
    licensing requirements may limit the systems that data captured using certain questionnaires may be shared with.
  </p>

	<a name="disclaimer"> </a>
	<h3>Disclaimer</h3>
	<p>
    The specification herewith documented is a demo working specification, and may not be used for any implementation purposes. 
    This draft is provided without warranty of completeness or consistency, and the official publication supersedes this draft.
    No liability can be inferred from the use or misuse of this specification, or its consequences.
  </p>
</div>